Matthew Lewis

Address 9 Tredwell Close **Phone** (+44) 7909977421

London, SW2 3JZ Email matthew@mglewis.co.uk

Website mglewis.co.uk

Personal Profile

Enthusiastic software developer and systems engineer. Creator or custom Java applications and CI amoungst a variety platforms and systems. Has been known to develop software for fun in his spare time.

Likely to be found on evenings and weekends bouldering, playing football or watching cricket.

Employment History

2015 - **UBS - Authorised Officer**

Software Engineer and Product Owner

- Responsible for a portfolio of custom and 3rd party applications.
- Managed team of offshore software developers.
- Delivered IBM Business Process Manager to the UBS environment.

Technologies: Java, Jenkins, Linux, Git, Swift, Nexus, Shell, Oracle

2013 - 2014 **UBS - Non Officer**

Software Engineer

- Sucessfully delivered a complete stack upgrade of EMC Documentum 7.1.
- Developed a number of high performance custom Java components.
- Drove team adoption of best practices: VC, CI, Automated Testing, Release Management.

Technologies: Java, Jenkins, Linux, Solaris, Tomcat, Websphere, Ant, Shell, Oracle

2011 - 2013 UBS - Graduate Trainee

Analyst

- Developed VBA and Tableau reporting systems.
- Designed and implemented a series of automated tools for use by remote support teams.

Technologies: VBA, Tableau, SQL, BASH, Atlassian Suite.

Education

2008 - 2011 University of Bristol

2:1 Computer Science BSc (with Hons)